examtime.com 2016-06-11

# GoConqr - Privacy Policy

Examtime Limited (“we”) supply any and all of the services made available on our websites www.examtime.com and www.goconqr.com or any and all of our other related websites, any and all of their subdomains, any and all of their mobile versions, access to databases and content and the opportunity to create and share content (“the Service”). We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. 

This policy (together with our  Acceptable Use  and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. 

"Personal Data" is information relating to a living individual who can be identified from the information and it includes your name, email address or postal address. 

"Processing" includes when we obtain data from you, store your data, transfer your data or use your data to allow you to use this site. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act, 1988 (as amended) (the Act), the data controller is Examtime Limited of 2nd Floor, Unit 2B, Parkview House, Beech Hill Office Campus, Clonskeagh, Dublin 4. 

Our nominated representative for the purpose of the Act is Peter Buckley who can be contacted at the address above. 

##  INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU 

We may collect and process the following data about you: 

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Service. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Service, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by Examtime Limited, and when you report a problem with our Service. 
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. 
  * Details of transactions (that is, if you or with the consent of your parent or guardian decide to subscribe for any service or buy any product or service from us) you carry out through our site and of the fulfillment of any orders. 
  * Details of your visits to our Service including, but not limited to, age, gender traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access. This information may be collected through Google Analytics Advertising Features (Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform integrations, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). 

##  INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM THIRD PARTIES WITH YOUR CONSENT 

As part of our functionality we offer you the opportunity to connect with your friends who already use GoConqr. When selecting this option you give us authority to: 

  1. View your Facebook Friends and your contacts on GMail, Yahoo or Microsoft email services, 
  2. Compare these against our database of GoConqr users, and 
  3. Where there is a match, to offer you the option of connecting with your friend through GoConqr. 

When you choose the option to connect, your friend will have the opportunity to either accept or decline this connection request. All connections with Facebook, gmail, yahoo and Microsoft are done through their standard channels. We do not store any of these contact details. We may use the information we collect to: 

  * provide you with personalized content and services; 
  * customize and improve the features, performance, and support of the site. 

##  INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOUR COMPUTER 

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system of your computer and browser type of your computer, for our system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions (i.e. use of our Service) and patterns, and does not identify you or any individual. 

##  COOKIES 

Our Service uses "Cookies" to distinguish you from other users of our Service and to anonymously track visiting and browsing patterns. A Cookie is a small text file implanted by us and most other website operators (or an advertiser on this site) on the hard disk of your computer when you visit the site. Cookies can collect information about users of our Service like you, such as your names, address, e-mail details, passwords and your user preferences. While cookies and the information they obtain may not identify a living individual on their own, they may be able to do so in combination with other information held by us or a third party. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Service and also allows us to improve our site. The website uses session cookies for site navigation purposes. These cookies expire and are deleted at the end of a browsing session. We also use Google Analytics for tracking and data capture purposes. Data collected through cookies is always anonymous and aggregated. 

##  WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

The data that we collect from you will not be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area which consists of the European Union, Norway and Iceland ("EEA"). It will only be processed by staff operating in the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, processing your subscription, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. A server is a machine that amongst others stores and processes data or information. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Service or your account, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of or sending by you of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted or sent by you to our Service; any transmission or sending by you is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access _i.e._ access to your data by a person who should not have such access. 

##  ACCESSING THE SERVICE THROUGH OUR APPS 

The service is available to access through mobile applications. Our Apps use third party service providers to provide functionality to our users. 

The data gathered by the third party providers relates to the aggregate usage of our service and does not contain personal identifiable data. 

These third party service providers may transfer, store and use the data in the United States and any other country in which they operate. 

Privacy and Data protection laws in some of these countries may vary from the laws of the Country in which you live. 

##  USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION 

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

  * To ensure that content from our Service is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 
  * To carry out our obligations or duties arising from any contracts or subscriptions entered into between you and us. 
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so. 
  * To notify you about changes to our services. 

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by email, post or telephone. 

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 users in the United Kingdom have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, users in London). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience. 

##  DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION 

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group of companies, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in Part 1 of the Irish Companies Act 2014. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties: 

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets, although that prospective seller or buyer would be requested not to disclose such personal data. 
  * If Examtime Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. 
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Acceptable Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Examtime Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

##  YOUR RIGHTS 

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [contactus@goconqr.com](mailto:contactus@goconqr.com) . 

You may click [ here ](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to opt out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features. 

Our Service may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

##  ACCESS TO INFORMATION 

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £5 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

##  PRIVACY OF CHILDREN 

Our services and products are not targeted at children under thirteen (13) years of age. If you are under 13 years old you will not be allowed to open an account on our Service or subscribe for any or our services. If we discover that we hold or have inadvertently disclosed any personally identifiable data for any user or customer under 13 years of age, it will be deleted from our system to ensure the privacy of the child. 

##  SAFEGUARDING CHILDREN’S PERSONAL DATA 

We also have a number of protections dealing with the personal data of persons under 18 years of age. These are that a guardian or parent has the right to review the personal data the Service has collected from their child, have their child’s personal data deleted from the site and also request us to cease obtaining further personal data from the child going forward. To do so if you are the parent or guardian of a child either post or send by fax to us an affidavit, along with a copy of your driver’s license or passport, to the address or fax number below: 

  * Examtime Limited, 2nd Floor, Unit 2B, Parkview House, Beech Hill Office Campus, Clonskeagh, Dublin 4, Ireland. 
  * Ireland: + 353 1 679 5047. 

The affidavit must be signed by and in the presence of a notary public who is a person qualified to have documents sworn under oaths. Your affidavit must confirm: 

  * You are the parent or guardian; 
  * Your child is under the age of eighteen years; 
  * Whether you would like to have the right to review the information the site has collected from your child, have your child’s personal data deleted from the site and/or request us to stop collecting further personal data from your child in the future. 
  * Your child’s username or account name; 
  * Your e-mail address. 

When we receive the affidavit we will be able to carry out your instructions. If you are submitting an affidavit in relation to a child under 13 years of age, then please do not include any of their personal data. If you do include any personal data of the child, your request is your instruction for us to receive and store the personal data as reasonably necessary to fulfil your request. 

##  CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY 

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. This page was last updated on 8th April 2016. 

##  CONTACT 

We are incorporated in Ireland under company number 495899 and have our registered office at 2nd Floor, Unit 2B, Parkview House, Beech Hill Office Campus, Clonskeagh, Dublin 4, Ireland. Our main trading address is 2nd Floor, Unit 2B, Parkview House, Beech Hill Office Campus, Clonskeagh, Dublin 4, Ireland. 

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [contactus@goconqr.com](mailto:contactus@goconqr.com) .
